Guide to the National Guardian Photographs PHOTOS.213
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Education Post War, 1969-1975 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Military Post War, 1975-1975 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Children Post War, 1975-1975 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Medical Care Post War, 1975-1975 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Industry Post War, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder 43053)
- Culture Post War, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Reconstruction Post War, 1975-1975 (Box 62, Folder 1-3)
- Army of Vietnam During War, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder 4-6)
- All About Viet-Gong, 1949-1974 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Deconstruction Defoliation During War, 1966-1975 (Box 62, Folder 8-9)
- Vietnam Photos, 1963-1975 (Box 62, Folder 10-13)
- Politics Post War, 1972-1986 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Yen Truong Co-operative, 1975-1975 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- A, 1971-1971 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Muhammed Ali, 1955-1985 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Isabel Allende, 1968-1975 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Salvador Allende, undated (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Herbert Aptheker, 1964-1972 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Yasser Arafat, 1963-1969 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- James Aronson, 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Ralph Abernathy, 1949-1988 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Bella Abzug, 1968-1973 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Spiro Agnew, 1971-1986 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- B, 1970-1974 (Box 63, Folder 12-13)
- B Politician G.O.P./Dems/Civil Rights Activists, etc., 1954-1987 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Joan Baez, 1966-1986 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Cedric Belfrage, 1966-1975 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Daniel Berrigan and Phil Berrigan, 1953-1989 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Maurice Bishop, 1968-1987 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Ann and Carl Braden, 1979-1979 (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Leonid Breezhnez, 1958-1967 (Box 63, Folder 20)
- H. Rap Brown, 1971-1971 (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Simone de Bouvoir, 1967-1973 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Burchett Booklet, 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Wilfred Burchett, 1960-1965 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Manny Bloch – Rosenberg's Lawyer, 1964-1988 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Political C, 1953-1954 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous C, 1967-1986 (Box 64, Folder 42893)
- Rubin Carter, 1964-1989 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Stokely Carmichael, 1975-1976 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Lt. William Calley (and friends), 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- George Washington Carver, 1969-1970 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Fidel Castro, 1937-1948 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Chiang Ching (Mao's wife), 1959-1974 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Angela Davis, undated (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Misc. D, 1970-1973 (Box 64, Folder 15-16)
- Richard J. Daley, 1950-1990 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Ron Dellums, 1970-1975 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Barbara Dane, 1971-1988 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Ben Davis, 1967-1967 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Rennie Davis, undated (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Clifton DeBerry, 1969-1971 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- E.V. Debs, 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Dave Dellinger, 1980-1980 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Isaac Deutscher, 1969-1976 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Dinkins, 1958-1966 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Cuba Usvaido Dorticos, 1989-1989 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- William Douglas, 1959-1962 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Duarte, 1964-1975 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- W.E.B. Dubois, undated (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Bob Dylan, 1948-1988 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Mike Dukakis, 1967-1969 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous E, 1988-1988 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- Cyrus Eaton, 1964-1988 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Dr. Kenneth Edelin, 1958-1966 (Box 65, Folder 18)
- Albert Einstein, 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- Charles Evers, 1946-1961 (Box 65, Folder 20)
- W, 1968-1974 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- Waldheim, 1962-1988 (Box 65, Folder 22)
- Wallace, 1971-1979 (Box 65, Folder 23)
- Bill Walton, 1972-1975 (Box 65, Folder 24)
- Harold Washington See also Illinois, 1975-1975 (Box 65, Folder 25)
- General William Westmoreland, 1983-1987 (Box 65, Folder 26)
- Wilson, Brian, 1965-1975 (Box 65, Folder 27)
- Robert F Williams, 1990-1990 (Box 65, Folder 28)
- Woodcock, 1961-1975 (Box 65, Folder 29)
- X, 1970-1974 (Box 65, Folder 30)
- Y, 1964-1987 (Box 65, Folder 31)
- Andy Young – U.N., 1957-1974 (Box 65, Folder 32)
- Yabionski Case, 1970-1972 (Box 65, Folder 33)
- Cedric Belfrage Memorial, 1969-1972 (Box 65, Folder 34)
- Z, 1990-1990 (Box 65, Folder 35)
- Military, U.S., 1963-1975 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- U.S. Spy Planes Downed in USSR (Espionage), 1959-1974 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Troops and Maneuvers (Armed Forces), 1960-1969 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Powers – U-2 Incident (Espionage), 1962-1975 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- G.I. Civilian Demonstrations – On and Off Base (Armed Forces), 1960-1962 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Generals and Admirals, 1967-1971 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Atom Radiation, 1948-1974 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Missiles, 1960-1964 (Box 66, Folder 42956)
- Weaponry – Aircraft (Armed Forces), 1957-1968 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Weaponry – Ships, Carriers, Destroyers (Armed Forces), 1964-1976 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Satellites-Science and Technology, 1952-1975 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- NASA, 1962-1967 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Security/Surveillance, 1961-1967 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Joint Chiefs of Staff – (past and present), 1957-1970 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Defense Dept., 1967-1970 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Defections, 1962-1962 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Various Armed Forces Crimes and Court-martials, 1960-1967 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Gen. George C. Marshall, 1967-1972 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- G.I.s and Army, 1947-1953 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Weaponry – Atomic (Armed Forces), 1967-1974 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Alleged U.S. Spys [sic] (Espionage), 1945-1967 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Alleged Spys [sic] for Communist Countries (Espionage), 1959-1967 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- GI Movement, 1960-1966 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Draft Resistance, 1966-1972 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Pueblo Incident (Espionage), 1968-1974 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- V.E. Day, 1969-1969 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Concentration Camps, 1945-1973 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Children Of War, 1945-1945 (Box 67, Folder 15)
- Iran/Contra Scandal Hearings, 1986-1986 (Box 67, Folder 16)
- Left Confabs, 1987-1987 (Box 67, Folder 17)
- Robots, 1985-1986 (Box 67, Folder 18)
- Rock-N-Roll, undated (Box 67, Folder 19)
- Sanctuary, 1985-1985 (Box 67, Folder 20)
- Sexuality, 1985-1986 (Box 67, Folder 21)
- Social Security, 1983-1985 (Box 67, Folder 22)
- Socialist Workers Party, 1935-1985 (Box 67, Folder 23)
- Space/Star Wars, 1988-1988 (Box 67, Folder 24)
- Sports, 1971-1986 (Box 67, Folder 25)
- "Spying" FBI, CIA, etc., 1981-1986 (Box 67, Folder 26)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- AK, 1971-1984 (Box 67, Folder 27)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- AZ, 1985-1985 (Box 67, Folder 28)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- CO, 1985-1985 (Box 67, Folder 29)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- CA, 1987-1987 (Box 67, Folder 30)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- D.C, 1983-1983 (Box 67, Folder 31)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- DE, 1984-1984 (Box 67, Folder 32)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- FL, 1985-1985 (Box 67, Folder 33)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- IA, 1985-1985 (Box 67, Folder 34)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- ID, 1986-1986 (Box 67, Folder 35)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- IL, 1985-1985 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- IN, 1984-1989 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- LA, 1986-1989 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- MA, 1985-1985 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- MI, 1983-1986 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- MN, 1984-1987 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- MISCELLANEOUS, 1985-1985 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- MT, 1988-1988 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- NH, 1985-1985 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- SD, 1985-1985 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- TN, undated (Box 68, Folder 11)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- TX, undated (Box 68, Folder 12)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- VA, 1982-1984 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- VT, 1984-1984 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians -- WI, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Teaching, 1983-1988 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Technology and Science, 1985-1985 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- Tenants Rights, 1959-1973 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- Transit, 1988-1988 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- Unemployment/Graphics, 1983-1985 (Box 68, Folder 20)
- Women, 1968-1971 (Box 68, Folder 21-22)
- Weaponry –Tanks, Artillery (Armed Forces), 1973-1986 (Box 68, Folder 23)
- Welfare, 1956-1984 (Box 68, Folder 24)
- States, Locales, Local Politicians /NY, 1968-1969 (Box 68, Folder 25)
- Veterans/ POWs, 1984-1987 (Box 68, Folder 26)
- Utilities and Public Workers, 1985-1987 (Box 68, Folder 27)
- Watsonville Strike, CA 1985, 1986 Peter Maiden Photos, 1984-1984 (Box 68, Folder 28)
- War Toys, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 29)
- Welfare Workers, 1985-1985 (Box 68, Folder 30)
- Woolworth, 1965-1973 (Box 68, Folder 31)
- WBAI, 1985-1985 (Box 68, Folder 32)
- Women in Sports, 1986-1986 (Box 68, Folder 33)
- Temp Boorfile, 1973-1974 (Box 68, Folder 34)
- Workers – Miscellaneous, 1986-1986 (Box 68, Folder 35)
- Workers – Miscellaneous, 1947-1985 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Women in Workforce, 1947-1985 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- US/USSR, 1971-1985 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Aircraft Workers, 1983-1983 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Auto Workers, 1945-1975 (Box 69, Folder 5-7)
- AFL-CIO, 1952-1976 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Automation-Technology, 1953-1975 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Boeing Strike, 1957-1969 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Clerical Workers, 1989-1989 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Clerical Workers/ Yale Strike, 1961-1984 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Communication Workers Telephone – TV – Radio, 1984-1985 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Construction Workers, 1952-1972 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Eastern, 1964-1988 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Electrical Workers, 1989-1989 (Box 70, Folder 6-7)
- Farmworkers Migrant Sharecroppers, 1948-1970 (Box 70, Folder 8-9)
- United Farmworkers, 1956-1982 (Box 70, Folder 43019)
- UFW Cesar Chavez, 1941-1975 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- United Farmworkers, 1966-1975 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- UFW – Support Demonstrations, 1966-1985 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Garment and Textile, 1965-1977 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Government Workers, 1952-1978 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Hormel P-N (Meatpackers), 1953-1975 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Hospital Workers, 1986-1986 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Hospital Workers (1199), 1965-1988 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Hotel Workers, 1984-1989 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Steel Workers, 1988-1988 (Box 71, Folder 9-11)
- Steel Workers, 1925-1986 (Box 72, Folder 1-4)
- Airline Strikes, 1925-1986 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Abraham Lincoln Brigade, 1985-1985 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- A.I.D.S., 1936-1936 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Alliance for Cultural Democracy Conference, 1985-1988 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Animal Rights/Animal Cruelty, 1986-1986 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Arms Tacks and Arms Control, 1986-1986 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Asbestos, 1984-1985 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Auto Industry, 1987-1987 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Aviation Industry – see also Military Hardware, 1970-1984 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Asian Americans, undated (Box 72, Folder 14)
- Tawana Brawley Case, 1984-1984 (Box 72, Folder 15)
- Black Struggle – Freedom Ride 1986, 1988-1988 (Box 72, Folder 16)
- Black Capitalism, 1986-1986 (Box 72, Folder 17)
- U.S. Blacks 3rd World Solidarity, 1989-1989 (Box 72, Folder 18)
- Black Leaders Meet at Southern, 1987-1987 (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Leaders – Black, 1987-1987 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Black Personalities, 1963-1987 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Black History/Personalities, 1967-1986 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Black Struggles, 1948-1985 (Box 73, Folder 42798)
- Black Struggle (N.Y. 8), 1963-1986 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Black Life, 1985-1985 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Central Hall Artists, 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Censorship, 1985-1985 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Chemical Warfare, 1984-1984 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Children/Childcare, 1959-1959 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Chinatown, 1954-1986 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Civil Rights, 1985-1985 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Cities Decay, 1985-1985 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Chrysler Corporation, undated (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Congress, 1955-1974 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- House: Republicans (Congress), 1983-1983 (Box 73, Folder 16)
- Senate: Democrats (Congress), undated (Box 73, Folder 17)
- Counterrevolutionaries, undated (Box 73, Folder 18)
- Color Purple Forum, 1982-1985 (Box 73, Folder 19)
- Demonstrations Death Penalty, 1986-1986 (Box 73, Folder 20)
- House:Democrats (Congress), 1985-1985 (Box 73, Folder 21)
- Dinkins Campaign, 1984-1984 (Box 73, Folder 22)
- Disabled, 1988-1989 (Box 73, Folder 23)
- Domestic History, 1978-1985 (Box 73, Folder 24)
- Draft, 1915-1966 (Box 73, Folder 25)
- Democrats, 1984-1985 (Box 73, Folder 26)
- Drugs, 1984-1984 (Box 73, Folder 27)
- Economy (U.S.) Budget, 1989-1989 (Box 73, Folder 28)
- Elderly, 1985-1985 (Box 73, Folder 29)
- Education/Daycare, 1963-1987 (Box 73, Folder 30)
- Elections, 1977-1987 (Box 73, Folder 31)
- Energy Not Nuclear see Nuke Energy, 1966-1983 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- ERA, 1986-1986 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Esmeralda, 1977-1980 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Environment, 1986-1986 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Peace Conferences, 1984-1988 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Pre-'60s Anti-War Demonstrations and Protests, 1947-1952 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Peace – 1967 Stockholm Sweden War Crimes Tribunal John Paul Sartre, Isaac Deutscher, etc., 1950-1971 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Various Demonstrations/Parades in NYC, 1967-1967 (Box 74, Folder 42956)
- Housing, 1953-1962 (Box 74, Folder 10-11)
- Ban the Bomb Demonstrations, 1949-1970 (Box 75, Folder 1-2)
- South Africa – Demos/U.S., 1957-1961 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Third World Solidarity-Demonstrations, 1970-1978 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- U.S. Demonstrations on Palestine, 1967-1979 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Labor History, 1973-1978 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Maritime Workers, 1908-1974 (Box 75, Folder 7-9)
- Maritime Workers, 1948-1984 (Box 76, Folder 1-8)
- Labor – miscellaneous, 1948-1984 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Lumberjacks, 1963-1986 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Machinists, 1962-1962 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Mining – Copper/Zinc, 1986-1986 (Box 76, Folder 12-13)
- Labor: Miners, 1950-1967 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Mine Workers, 1961-1983 (Box 77, Folder 2-8)
- Mine Workers Pittston Strike Recent, 1951-1978 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Mining Disasters, 1989-1989 (Box 77, Folder 10-11)
- Miscellaneous Workers, 1947-1972 (Box 78, Folder 1-3)
- Newspaper Guilds, 1956-1986 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Newspaper Workers, 1985-1985 (Box 78, Folder 5-8)
- Paperworkers, 1920-1989 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- PATCO/Hormel, 1987-1989 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Postal Workers, 1966-1986 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Oil and Gas Workers, 1955-1978 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Restaurant/Hotel Workers, 1952-1975 (Box 78, Folder 13)
- Railroad Workers, 1989-1989 (Box 78, Folder 14)
- Sanitation, 1951-1971 (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Run-away Shops, 1941-1975 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Demonstrations – Puerto Rico, 1986-1988 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Puerto Ricans /U.S., 1976-1988 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Puerto Rico – U.S. Demonstrations, 1964-1984 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Puerto Rico, 1964-1977 (Box 79, Folder 5-8)
- NYC – Power Blackout Nov. 1965, 1949-1986 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- NYC – Blackout 1977, 1965-1965 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- New York City Scenes, 1977-1977 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- Nixon Cabinet, 1960-1966 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- Watergate – Impeach, 1972-1975 (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Watergate – Impeach, 1972-1974 (Box 80, Folder 43102)
- Watergate, 1972-1974 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Washington Admininstration (Watergate etal), 1973-1973 (Box 80, Folder 42830)
- Assassinations, 1973-1974 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Attica, 1963-1978 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- American Bar Association, 1971-1975 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Baltimore Two, 1963-1963 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Berrigan/Kissinger, 1976-1976 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Calley/Medina, 1968-1972 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- Capital Punishment – Legal System, 1969-1971 (Box 80, Folder 12)
- CIA/FBI, 1960-1960 (Box 80, Folder 13)
- Chicago 8 Trial, 1963-1976 (Box 80, Folder 14)
- DACAJEWEIAH (John Hill), 1968-1970 (Box 80, Folder 15)
- Death Penalty, 1977-1977 (Box 80, Folder 16)
- Filipino Nurses, 1972-1977 (Box 80, Folder 17)
- Grand Jury Abuse, 1977-1977 (Box 80, Folder 18)
- Hollywood 10, 1976-1977 (Box 80, Folder 19)
- HUAC, 1947-1959 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Willie McGee Trial/Execution, 1951-1965 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Rev. W. Melish, 1951-1951 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Milwaukee 14, 1956-1974 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Tom Mooney, 1969-1969 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- My Lai, 1931-1942 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- NY 8+, 1969-1972 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Oakland 7, 1982-1985 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Oswald/Warren Report, 1969-1969 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- Pendleton 14, 1959-1964 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- James Earl Ray, 1977-1977 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Jack Ruby Trial, 1968-1969 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- Assata Shakur, 1962-1965 (Box 81, Folder 13)
- Morton Sobell, 1972-1982 (Box 81, Folder 14)
- Sacco and Vanzetti, 1954-1969 (Box 81, Folder 15)
- Scopes "Monkey Trial", 1923-1959 (Box 81, Folder 16)
- SLA, 1957-1965 (Box 81, Folder 17)
- Martin Sostre, 1974-1975 (Box 81, Folder 18)
- S-Q 6 Trial, 1960-1969 (Box 81, Folder 19)
- Weather Underground, 1971-1977 (Box 81, Folder 20)
- Trials – miscl., 1970-1970 (Box 81, Folder 21)
- Air Pollution, 1969-1975 (Box 81, Folder 22)
- Dams and Irrigation (conservation), 1954-1973 (Box 81, Folder 23)
- Ecology, 1940-1966 (Box 81, Folder 24)
- Energy, U.S., 1954-1974 (Box 81, Folder 25-26)
- Military Weapons, 1970-1977 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Nuclear, 1957-1971 (Box 82, Folder 42769)
- Nuclear Energy and Weapons, 1964-1980 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Panther Trials, 1971-1979 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Police, 1969-1971 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Police Brutality, 1965-1974 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Police Demonstration, 1972-1985 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Prison and Prisoners – Legal System, 1963-1975 (Box 82, Folder 42988)
- Soledad – San Quentin, 1947-1977 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Students for Democratic Society – Organizations and Groups, 1970-1972 (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Supreme Court Portraits, 1968-1969 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- International Organizations, 1953-1977 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- Australia, 1975-1985 (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Canada, 1955-1975 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- New Zealand, 1963-1975 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Europe, 1983-1983 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- European Common Market, 1971-1978 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- North Atlantic Treaty Organization – NATO, 1961-1967 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Albania, 1963-1969 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Austria, 1962-1975 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Belgium, 1951-1972 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Britain, 1945-1974 (Box 83, Folder 42988)
- England, 1959-1975 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Bulgaria, 1967-1975 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Czechoslovakia: 1968, Soviet Invasion, 1947-1969 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Czechoslovakia: 1968, Soviet Invasion, 1968-1968 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Czechoslovakia, 1968-1968 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Finland, 1947-1969 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- France – Demonstrations, protests, 1983-1983 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- France – miscellaneous, 1985-1985 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- France – Personalities, 1986-1986 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- France: Racism, 1984-1984 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- E. Germany, 1984-1988 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- West Germany, 1969-1982 (Box 84, Folder 42988)
- West German Left, 1917-1975 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Greece, 1983-1986 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Holland, 1973-1984 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Ireland, 1984-1984 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- Italy – miscellaneous, 1973-1985 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Portugal, 1950-1987 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Romania, 1974-1976 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Scotland, 1983-1983 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Spain, undated (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Sweden, 1972-1986 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Turkey, undated (Box 85, Folder 7)
- U.S.S.R., 1959-1988 (Box 85, Folder 8-9)
- Yugoslavia, 1943-1973 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Korea's War – China, 1979-1987 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- US and China, 1948-1958 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- US and China, 1959-1975 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Cultural Revolution China, 1959-1975 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- War With Japan – China, 1966-1967 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Revolutions– China, 1940-1946 (Box 86, Folder 4-6)
- Commerce – China, 1945-1949 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- China – Agriculture, 1960-1976 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Madam Sun-Yat Sen, 1958-1975 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Demonstrations and Congress China, 1944-1955 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Demonstrations and Congress China, 1951-1975 (Box 87, Folder 1-2)
- China – U.N., National Day, 1951-1975 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Peasants – China, 1970-1972 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Industry – China, 1951-1975 (Box 87, Folder 5-8)
- Industry – China, 1951-1975 (Box 88, Folder 1-3)
- Political, Diplomatic Figures – China, 1951-1975 (Box 88, Folder 4-7)
- Military – China, 1943-1976 (Box 88, Folder 42956)
- Education – China, 1949-1975 (Box 89, Folder 42737)
- Children – China, 1958-1975 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Africa-General, 1952-1975 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Algeria, 1973-1986 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Angola, 1963-1975 (Box 89, Folder 42893)
- Angola, 1961-1976 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Angola – US Demonstrations, 1958-1988 (Box 89, Folder 9)
- Bechuanaland – Africa Botswana, 1972-1976 (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Burundi, 1965-1965 (Box 89, Folder 11)
- Cameroon, undated (Box 89, Folder 12)
- Cape Verde Island, 1956-1962 (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Chad, 1963-1975 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Congo, 1972-1972 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Dahomey, 1961-1972 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Eritrean Relief Committee, Inc., 1968-1968 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Eritrea, 1978-1986 (Box 90, Folder 5-8)
- Ethiopia, 1977-1986 (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Gabon, 1963-1990 (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Gambia, 1974-1974 (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Ghana, 1965-1975 (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Guinea and Guinea-Bissau, 1960-1966 (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Eritrea and the Horn of Africa, 1960-1973 (Box 90, Folder 14)
- Ivory Coast, 1965-1977 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Kenya, 1962-1973 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Lesotho, 1961-1987 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Liberia, 1966-1973 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Libya, 1961-1974 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Malawi, 1960-1983 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Mali, 1960-1962 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Mauritania, 1962-1986 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Morocco, 1974-1976 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- Sahara, 1954-1975 (Box 91, Folder 10)
- Mozambique, 1975-1976 (Box 91, Folder 11)
- Namibia, 1975-1989 (Box 91, Folder 12)
- Natal, 1973-1986 (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Niger, 1972-1972 (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Nigeria, 1973-1974 (Box 91, Folder 15)
- Uman, 1966-1973 (Box 91, Folder 16)
- Sao Tome and Principe, 1972-1972 (Box 91, Folder 17)
- Senegal (Mali Federation), 1975-1975 (Box 91, Folder 18)
- Somalia, 1960-1976 (Box 91, Folder 19)
- South Africa, 1966-1980 (Box 92, Folder 1-2)
- Sudan, 1963-1989 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Tanzania, 1970-1987 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Togo, 1964-1987 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Tunisia, 1958-1977 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Uganda, 1955-1961 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Upper Volta, 1962-1986 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Western Sahara, 1973-1974 (Box 92, Folder 9-12)
- Zaire, 1973-1988 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Zambia, 1960-1971 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Zanzibar, 1965-1966 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Zimbabwe (Rhodesia), 1963-1964 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Latin America, 1959-1984 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Organization of American States – OAS, 1962-1980 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- OAS Punta Del Este Conference, 1960-1969 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Anguilla, 1962-1962 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Barbados, 1969-1969 (Box 93, Folder 9)
- Bermuda, 1966-1969 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Bolivia, 1960-1970 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Brazil, 1963-1974 (Box 93, Folder 12)
- Chile, 1958-1972 (Box 94, Folder 1-6)
- Colombia, 1956-1987 (Box 94, Folder 7)
- Costa Rica, 1960-1972 (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Curacao, 1955-1975 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- Ecuador, 1969-1969 (Box 94, Folder 10)
- El Salvador, 1955-1976 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- El Salvador, 1962-1990 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- El Salvador (Earthquake), 1962-1990 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Refugees/El Salvador outside U.S., 1986-1986 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Grenada, 1984-1984 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Guatemala, 1980-1984 (Box 95, Folder 5-6)
- Refugees/Guatemalan outside U.S., 1954-1985 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Guyana, 1982-1982 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Haiti, 1953-1964 (Box 95, Folder 9-12)